<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>

	<!--BASIC MESSAGES (UNUSED)-->
	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic1">
		<text>Hey man, this made me think of you...</text>
	</string>
	
    <string id="st_gfcmod_basic2">
		<text>You know what? Thanks for the great times together, here's something for you</text>
	</string>	

    <string id="st_gfcmod_basic3">
		<text>Do you want this? I don't have any use for it</text>
	</string>

    <string id="st_gfcmod_basic4">
		<text>Yooo check it! Look what I found!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic5">
		<text>Hey, found something out there. Thought it might interest you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic6">
		<text>Here's a little something for you. Consider it a token of our adventures.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic7">
		<text>Found an interesting item. It's yours now.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic8">
		<text>Guess what I stumbled upon? It's a surprise, take it!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic9">
		<text>Found a little extra during my travels. Take this, my friend.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic10">
		<text>Got my hands on something. It's yours, no strings attached.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic11">
		<text>Gift from the Zone! Found this during my latest expedition.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic12">
		<text>Check it out! Something I found that might come in handy for you.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic13">
		<text>Found a little surprise for you. Enjoy!</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_basic14">
		<text>Gift time, my friend! Found something useful just for you.</text>
	</string>
	
	<!--STAGES MESSAGES-->
	
	<string id="st_gfcmod_bad1">
		<text>Hey! I found this. I don't really need it so I guess you can have it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_bad2">
		<text>Hey! Want this?</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_bad3">
		<text>I don't really trust you but we can still help each other. You can have this.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_bad4">
		<text>Hey, stumbled upon this. I don't need it, and you look like you could use a help.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_bad5">
		<text>Trust is earned, and I'm not there yet, but here, take this. Better you have it than the Zone swallows it.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_normal1">
		<text>In the Zone you need every help you can get. Found this, thought it might tip the odds.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_normal2">
		<text>It's not all anomalies and mutants with you around. Here, a little something for the road.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_normal3">
		<text>This place can eat you alive. Here's a small something to keep you one step ahead.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_normal4">
		<text>I appreciate the company. Found this lying around, thought you might make better use of it.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_normal5">
		<text>It's not all bad traveling with you. Here, take this. Consider it a rare gesture of kindness.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_good1">
		<text>I've got your back, and I figured you could use this. Don't say I never did anything for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_good2">
		<text>You're not half bad to have around. Here, a little gift to show my appreciation.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_good3">
		<text>We make a decent team. Found this, thought it might be useful for you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_good4">
		<text>In this godforsaken place, allies are rare. Consider this a gesture of trust, Stalker.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_good5">
		<text>We're starting to click, aren't we? Here, a little something for the road.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_excellent1">
		<text>Trust like this is hard to come by. Here's a gift, a symbol of our unbroken bond.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_excellent2">
		<text>I'm glad we're on the same side. Found this and thought of you.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_excellent3">
		<text>You're one of the few I can trust out here. Here's a little something for you, my friend.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_excellent4">
		<text>You're not just a partner; you're a true friend. Take this as a thank you for being there.</text>
	</string>
	<string id="st_gfcmod_excellent5">
		<text>The trials of the Zone are easier with you around. This is for you, my trusted companion.</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_friendship_increase_basic">
		<text>Friendship increased:</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_friendship_increase_passive">
		<text>Spending time together increased the friendship in your squad:</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_friendship_increase_companion_death_good">
		<text>The death of your companion made your squad more close, friendship increased:</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_friendship_decrease_basic">
		<text>Friendship decreased:</text>
	</string>

	<string id="st_gfcmod_friendship_decrease_companion_death_bad">
		<text>The death of your companion destroyed the spirits of your squad, friendship halved:</text>
	</string>

</string_table>